(Leonard:)Everything all right?
(Penny:)Yeah. I guess.
(Leonard:)Just tell me.
(Penny:)It's just, when we were kissing,
(Penny:)I couldn't help but picture
you with that other girl.
(Leonard:)Oh, no.
(Leonard:)No, come on.
(Leonard:)I have a friend in you.
(Leonard:)You said so.
(Leonard:)You're right.
Just forget it.
(chuckles)
Yeah.
Okay, listen. Uh...
(Leonard:)If you're imagining that
it was sexy, it wasn't.
We-we were both drunk, and
she smelled like an ashtray.
(Leonard:)The boat was moving a lot,
so I chipped her tooth.
(Penny:)Did you feel guilty?
(Leonard:)No, she had
dental insurance.
(Penny:)Did you feel guilty
after kissing her?
(Leonard:)Yes. I felt guilty as
soon as it happened.
(Leonard:)I feel guilty
every time I see her.
(Penny:)What do you mean,
every time you see her?
(Leonard:)What... do I mean?